<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Dan Henrie]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Dan Henrie]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/dan-henrie/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 00:18:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/dan-henrie/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Built for Construction Leaders.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Built for Construction Leaders.</h1><p>Constructorator is a website dedicated to helping construction field hands learn, grow, collaborate and share information.</p><img src="http://www.constructorator.com/uploads/2/6/0/5/26059504/5476161.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.constructorator.com/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1a2cde00-b179-4446-8e62-d572e4e2d8c9</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 00:18:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[About Dan Henrie]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>About Dan Henrie</h1><p>I have been in the construction industry for twenty years where I started as a laborer and moved my way up to Superintendent. My first real construction job was working for a concrete forming company who specialized in horizontal shoring. After four years and moving up from labor to carpenter, I knew I wanted to get on larger projects and work for a general contractor who also self-performed the concrete, so I applied and got a job as an apprentice carpenter and worked on the Assembly Hall project, from there it was all uphill. I would go onto the next job (Main Street Parking Garage) as a lead carpenter. Next stop was in Vail Colorado, working on the Ritz Carlton Hotel as a foreman. Half way through that project, I started and finished the Ritz Clubhouse as a General Foreman. Over the next few years I would travel around going to jobs that "needed help" with schedule or budget issues. The first opportunity I was given as a Superintendent was on the exterior skin of a mountain resort job which lead to moving around from job to job running exterior skins. Even though I didn't mind working on exteriors, what I really enjoyed was running the concrete crews. So my next chance came on the Church History Library, followed by the Outpatient Pavilion. Then, onto one of my favorites... Tower 5 (The Regent @ City Creek Center). </p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/3f4928bbef74636ebd666a43e813fdd702152138.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/dan-henrie/about-dan-henrie/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8e9414f8-46e1-467a-adb4-8d9f636e6630</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 00:02:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/fb041a71-d650-40a7-99c2-feb269a67a04.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/dan-henrie/450100a8-5a2d-4066-9ac5-bfdcad7a5c41/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">450100a8-5a2d-4066-9ac5-bfdcad7a5c41</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 00:10:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>